他们进去了
- 这次能让我满意吗？ - 做出多少了？
大概13磅吧
- 闪一边去！ - 你他妈在跟我开玩笑吗？
- 别在这点着那东西，拿出去抽，乔乔 - 好吧
听着JT，我们之前商量好的一次交货50kg
你们自己去协商销路吧 这不是我们该操心的问题
丹尼说很高兴与你们合作
一切正常吗？
- 成交，同样飞机，同样飞行员，同样价格 - 很好
去他妈的破飞机，我们有20个纯爷们, 随便一个都能开车把货带到图森
但我的路线更安全，你决定吧 丹尼
听着，你虽然是我儿子
但我们按道尔顿的方法来办
所有人开始把货品打包 我们30分钟后离开快点，快点！
该我们了，出发！
DEA（美缉毒总署）,都别动！举起手来！
趴在地上！
快来个人确定一下 我在里面卧底探员的情况
你可是我们的一员啊，你这叛徒！
- 快走，快走！ - 这他妈怎么回事？
- 乔乔，我们快离开这! - 扔掉你们的武器!
他是我们的卧底！
都退下！
都他妈的退下！ 快把你们该死的武器给我放下！
去你们的，该死的条子！
所有单位注意！ 有两名嫌犯逃走，驾驶一绿色车辆,
向东南方向行驶，有探员跟随！ 重复，有探员跟随!
- 这狗娘养的！ - 再快点！
- 这帮警察都他妈都疯了! - 操！ 操！
你他妈疯了吗？ 你想这么玩吗？那就来吧!
快下车 丹尼! 快下车！
你这叛徒！混蛋！
扔掉枪！
快点，乔乔. 扔掉枪！
- 扔掉你的枪! - 有人受伤倒地!
离他远点!
你谋杀了我儿子！你这狗娘养的混蛋！
你死定了! 你的孩子也是！
本来已经结束了！
可他明明是要伸手拿枪 你知道我必须下令的 柏克
柏克! 柏克!
别就这样离开啊！柏克!
《片名：最后防线》
(两年后)
- 帽子真酷 - 谢了
- 把它还给我 - 你害怕了吗？
- 我说了，把它还给我 - 你想要吗？过来拿啊!
你能怎么做呢？哭吗？
来啊，哭啊
- 我跟你说了两遍 - 两遍什么啊？ 懦夫！
我说了两遍
没错，你不亲自做的话，这活就没法做好
这些木材都是你能买到的
我们有橡树木，长叶松...
还有凤尾松，也是我最喜欢的
你要是想买便宜破烂的，最好去IKEA家具
看看这些，都是要扔掉的剩料，真可惜
这些东西你每两年就要翻新一次，
- 真是太麻烦了，看看这一大堆 - 你好？
- 我这就过去 - 出什么事了吗？
是麦蒂在学校里惹了点小麻烦
- 你自己能做完吗？ - 嘿，我是来陪你 不是帮你做 柏克.
- 嘿 柏克 可别再惹出什么麻烦 - 嗯 你说的没错
冷静？凭什么让我冷静？
不，这一点都说不通！ 我要这事现在就得到解决！
- 别担心亲爱的，交给警长，他会解决好的 - 那人是谁？
你认识他吗？嗯？
- 我不知道 - 那就是那该死小女孩的她父亲吗？
- 柏克 先生吗？ - 发生什么事了？
麦蒂 没事，她就在教室里 请跟我来
我得看看我儿子
亲爱的你还好吗？很疼吗？一定很疼！
血都流到他的T恤上了 吉米 我们等会再去找那小婊子算账！
- 嘿！ - 嘿什么嘿？你想说什么吗？
- 我让他们离开了 - 警长怎么会在这？
来看着卡西.博丁 上回她就已经影响到了学校的正常教学
总有些人需要“特殊照顾”
- 顺便说一下，我是苏珊.赫奇，学校里的心理医生 - 菲尔.柏克.
听着，你女儿很棒！
你还好吗？
- 那么，到底怎么了？ - 我警告了他两次，像你教我的那样
班长说看见麦蒂狠狠地打泰迪 就像她知道自己在做什么一样
- 是他挑起的，他就是个恶霸 - 好了麦蒂
这也许是我的错，我教她要保护好自己
- 觉得教你女儿打架是个好主意？ - 那倒不是，
她只是学着去保护自己
嘿 麦蒂,你可以在门外等一会儿吗？
- 好的，老师 - 谢谢
你们为什么搬来这里住呢？ 对大多数人来说，这里有些偏远了
- 她想养一匹马 - 哈
麦蒂的妈妈在这附近长大，
这会是个不错的地方去开始新的生活
她的档案里写着你妻子不久前已经过世了
- 是去年的事 - 没错，那段时间对她来说很难熬
她妈妈之前已经病了有一阵子了
还有什么要问吗？
- 他为什么会找上我？ - 他找上你是因为他觉得你与众不同
- 可我并不是与众不同 - 不，对他来说是的
所以什么都没发生过是吗？ 这家伙还能在这散步呢
- 什么都没发生过 快点 去吧！ - 好吧，知道了!
- 喂，柏克 - 嘿，吉米
- 柏克 - 在车旁边等我
- 怎么了？ - 靠着车站好
- 别当孬种！吉米 - 吉米
请回到你的车上
- 你欠我儿子一句该死的道歉！ - 冷静点，我不想事态恶化
- 吉米 , 请回到你的车上 - 这有个该死的小婊子打了我儿子，
- 有人欠我们一句道歉！ - 说的没错!
别那么叫她好吗，别那么说 亲爱的 你先上车好吗？
- 别用你的背对着我！ - 快上车亲爱的
揍他  吉米 揍他！
逮捕他，警长，快逮捕他！
逮捕他！你他妈傻站那干嘛？
- 放开他! - 你他妈在干吗？
- 你他妈的在干吗？ - 卡西 别说了！
- 你要对他的行为不闻不问吗？ - 到车里去亲爱的
- 看起来不好 - 没事的
- 上车去 - 做点什么！
喘口气  吉米 我的天啊
这才对，快去吧！
- 我有麻烦了吗？ - 不不 我目睹了全过程，是他越过了底线
不过你有必要把他摔得那么惨吗？ 尤其是在他孩子面前
- 我向来都这样 - 她还好吗？
你还好吗？这么说你住在老马场那边？
- 你在镇上做什么呢？ - 请问你问这些有原因吗？
也许我只是为了表示友好，
也许我感到无聊或是我很好奇 这些都不重要，无所谓
- 我有权向你发问 - 我向你保证这种事不会再发生了 警长
老爸，那有几位老师一直在看着呢
- 你是个懦夫 - 你说什么？
我说，你他妈的就是个孬种
你就是那样的人
你让他们把我们当成白痴一样 在所有人面前
- 半小时后整个镇子都会知道这件事 - 听着，我失去了...
- 失去什么 吉米？  什么？ - 我失去了平衡！
- 呵，失去平衡，他把你摔倒按在地上 - 妈妈，别抱怨了
- 爸爸是为我才那么做的 - 有什么计划, 吉米？
什么计划也没有，基思 还跟着我们呢
去他的 基思！
他是怎么买了那辆车的，这就是我想知道的， 他到底是靠什么买了那辆车？
- 谁啊？ - 谁？ 你他妈问我是谁？
那个把你放倒的混蛋，你忘了吗？
天啊，他把你摔得太惨了
我得去见我哥哥
让我们把这件事当成是家庭事务好吗，卡西
那你叫他什么？
现在你就像个他妈的白痴一样
午安 快乐的小鸟们
为什么不把音乐关了呢？ 快他妈把音乐关了！
嘿，你多大了？
17 .
走吧，快出去！
- 他们一起吗？ - 不一起，快滚！
至于你们几个 ...
我的名字是 凯特.博丁 .
我没把你伤的很严重吧 先生
只是想让你们感受一下 如果你们不停下，
而是继续在我的林子里胡搞的话会发生什么
别这样 博丁，我们无意冒犯
只是自己找点乐子而已
这我倒没怀疑
只是开心一下，孩子们找点乐子而已
享受生活，庆祝一下
好吧，我现在警告你，
我车上有一桶5加仑的汽油，
我打算把它们灌进你那该死的喉咙里，
只要再让我发现你在我们小镇附近
偷偷摸摸的出现，搞些不正当勾当
快停下！
仔细听好了，
我不想杀你们几个小屁孩，
你们现在站起来，然后拔腿就跑
随便哪个方向，只要不是这里
- 听清了他吗？ - 是的
那现在都给我滚吧！
滚！快跑！
快跑！
这真他妈是幼稚园的工作
该死的小孩
准备好了吗？
- 我很好，爸爸 - 是吗？看我这记重拳
- 爸! 在开玩笑吗？ - 嘿
嘿，听着，
我很自豪你能保护好自己，
你教训了这孩子
听起来像辆摩托车，是小猫在叫吗？
- 爸爸 - 怎么了？
今天你当时害怕吗？
- 说实话！ - 有一点害怕没什么不对的
- 可是为什么你看起来一点都不怕？ - 经验多了
- 晚安 , 卢瑟 - 爸爸，
- 是的？ - 你觉得赫奇小姐怎么样？
- 我觉得他还好啊 - 你懂我意思的
- 是的，我想我懂你的意思晚安啦 - 晚安
该死!
- 听着，你需要冷静 - 我需要冷静？
你觉得我们可以被某个白痴不尊重吗？
嘿，我不想这么说，可是...
把你丈夫放倒在地上这件事 也没什么大不了的
- 当他和基思交谈时，我听到他们说... - 你说什么？ 警长也在那？
我听到他们说他住在老马场那边
- 该死的！ - 你能去一趟那然后做些什么吗？
- 做些什么？ - 扰乱他们的生活，吓吓他们，你懂得
嘿，老大，今晚一切还好吗？
我等下再跟你们两个说好吗
很高兴再次见到你 卡西.
- 这俩人又哪不对了？ - 别理他们
他们就是些可笑的猴子
- 嘿，你看起来很焦虑 - 我知道啊
我需要一些“药品”，小剂量就行
好让让身体先冷静下来
想让我求你吗？
不
你看 如果我能控制住 你就能控制住，对吗？
嗯
- 我会解决那个柏克的问题的 - 谢谢
策划孩子的生日宴会 是件很麻烦的大事，
- 我们很高兴能帮你 - 谢谢了
我并不是很擅长这些
别担心，还有我呢，会很有趣的
是啊，她的确很喜欢你 苏珊张口闭口都是你
- 能抽空多和她聊聊吗？ - 当然，没问题
麦蒂 以前总是和她妈妈一聊就是几个小时
- 我想她最好还是能和女士多聊聊 - 我会很高兴那么做的
- 谢谢你！ - 还有件事，
- 镇上的居民有时可能会做出些愚蠢的事情 - 意思是？
就像阿巴拉锲亚山脉一样，麻烦不断
并且你人生地不熟
所以我觉得也许这样对麦蒂最好
如果你能远离麻烦的话 人们很快就会接受你
就只是因为两个孩子打架吗？
他们已经打到急诊室了
我甚至不知道这镇上还有急诊室
原来你这么觉得
最近大家都在谈论你
觉得你是个谜
远离麻烦，记住了
你来这有什么事吗？我可不觉得
你看，发生的那件事情 我们不想再惹麻烦了
是你孩子挑起来的 不是我儿子，是你女儿
我能做些什么 好让这件事平息呢？
你？
我要你道歉，全面道歉
我要你向我老婆道歉 因为你该那么做
还有我儿子 他看到了事件的全过程
- 我为所发生的事向你道歉 - 还要向他们道歉
同样向他们道歉
我们和好了吗， 吉米？
好了，你走吧
足够了
你先自己加油吧，我很快就过来
该死的冷冻器!
看看这是谁，
让我来处理他吧
嗨，你好啊 邻居
- 我能用一下吗？ - 我马上就好
可我现在就要用，你懂吗？
- 有什么需要帮忙的吗？ - 不，我们不需要你帮忙
他已经完了
恰古 关掉
- 一共 12.84 美元，先生 - 可我还没加完呢
我想已经完了
不管你怎么想，重新考虑一下
重新考虑，他要我重新考虑
你不会想打开开关吧
该死的！
你死定了
现在 给我走到街道上
然后让我好好的修理你
- 他们是镇上的人吗？ - 我从没见过他们
谁指使你来的？
没有人
把那拿过来
倒进去
怎么了？
什么？ 怎么会搞成这样的？
不过是我外甥学校里一个孩子的家长罢了 我怎么会知道
好吧好吧，我自己会处理的，该死的！
爸爸，你的手怎么了？
- 你自己看 - 是啊，这个...
我和第特计划把一些生锈的栅栏 搬到马棚后面时划伤的
最后还是搞定了
午安 介意下车聊两句吗？
小美女你可以呆在车里，不会耽误太久的
有什么问题吗，警长？
我接到一起关于加油站斗殴事件的报告 对此你知道些什么吗？
有什么人被起诉了吗？
- 不，没人被起诉 - 哦，那我们就没什么好聊的了
你是什么身份，什么背景？
前陆战队员？ 前警探？到底是什么？
都有可能吧，前探员什么的...
但标准答案 可能是些你不需要知道的结果
我可能是有些故事吧 可你真的不需要知道
可有些事你必须知道 柏克
你已经引起我的注意了
别自作聪明
今天还会领先我吗？
我想是的
- 今天在学校有交到新朋友吗？ - 是的，遇到了好多新朋友
- 今天在科学课上学到了很多很酷的知识 - 我不相信
你知道柏树能长多高吗？
- 它们能长到30多米 - 确实很酷
- 不，没有关于毒蛇的知识酷! - 毒蛇吗？
有蝮蛇，响尾蛇...
- 和眼镜蛇 - 还有眼镜王蛇，对吗？
不，眼镜王蛇都生活在远东地区
这下放心多了
- 爸爸？ - 嗯？
- 我们为什么搬到这来住？ - 因为这里没有眼镜蛇
来吧，看看四周 漂亮的橡树林，美丽的河流...
我还有什么好奢求的呢？
Wi-Fi
- Wi-Fi？ - 是啊，Wi-Fi
有人在家吗？
门是开着的，邻居来拜访你们了
局势很胶着啊
- 好吧 - 哈，或许罗
你知道" 葛芮 "吗？
- 在学校里的新朋友吗？ - 一个很惹人喜欢的女孩子
"葛芮"，嗯，是个不错的词
我觉得妈妈就是这样的
是啊，你的记性真不错 麦蒂
她确实是这样的
她的穿着，笑容 ...
她的一切
- 我想妈妈了 - 我也是
我太想她了，甚至觉得肚子疼
你知道，她总是担心着你的
她希望你生活得很快乐
只要你在身边我就很快乐
不然我还需要些什么呢？
- 快跟上 - 我一直在努力啊
路瑟!
放松，放松...
爸  爸!
- 你看见路瑟了吗？ - 路瑟？
- 没看到啊 - 我听不见它的铃声了，我要去找它
快回屋子去，你该准备睡觉了才对
别担心，我会找到它的，回去吧
- 爸爸你知道不抱着路瑟我睡不着的 - 我知道，可我需要你试一试好吗？
- 我会找到它的 - 还有小兔对吗？
是的，我会找到它们俩的
- 一切都会好起来的 - 好吧
路瑟! 小猫咪！
路瑟!
菲尔.柏克.
假发不错
在由丹尼.杜伟领导的机车匪帮"弃儿"担任卧底
哦，我的天啊
柏克...柏克...柏克...
很高兴认识你，柏克探员
路瑟!
路瑟! 快出来吧！
- 怎么了？ - 我想，我们有件大事要做了
大事？ 例如呢？
你尽快到我这来就好了
我3小时后才换班呢， 你要我开去什里夫波特吗？
好吧好吧，一大早就赶过来好吗
一切瞬息万变
还记得乔乔吗？ 乔乔.泰利
是 丹尼T 的儿子吗？ 我当然记得
- 那孩子就是个混蛋 - 他之前是
直到他被警方开了47枪打死
那是他唯一的儿子
听说丹尼T为此大动肝火，记恨于心
呀啊
不过他一直没抓到 那个害死他儿子的帮派成员
所以呢？
他不只是个帮派成员 其实是个卧底探员
自己看吧
我发现柏克 就是那个卧底探员
他的卧底身份是MC道尔.顿塔
有个卧底探员住在雷维尔？ 该死！你有没有想过...
别紧张，放松
我想他只是独自住在这里，带着他的女儿
相信我，这可是我们的机会
- 你在这干嘛呢 柏克？ - 把他关掉!
让我们废话少说，开门见山
昨天有人偷偷进入我们家，在我们外出时
- 我不知道你在说些什么 - 你觉得很有意思吗？
你他妈的觉得这很好玩吗？
你得到你要的道歉了 所以别再来招惹我们！
最好别让我再因为这事来这！
- 我要你还回我女儿的宠物猫！ - 宠物猫？
- 我不知道关于猫的什么事啊！ - 今天！
还有，离我们家远点！ 懂了吗？
很好
我们到这之后一切瞬息万变啊！
看到了吗，玻璃器皿...
金属，发动机，排气系统...
一切都在正常运转
那我们干嘛还要联系丹尼T？
我们会把那该死的卧底交给他
用来交换更多的销售通路
可是凯特 机车帮都是些人渣 不能信任他们！
你把他交给他们 你一转身他们就会杀了他，
- 而你什么也得不到 - 听好 这意味着我们不再做"小本生意"
不再有奸诈的中间人 我们所要做的就是生产 收益
- 永远都没有那么简单 - 不，你所需要做的只是...
找几个线人能让你和丹尼T的律师聊聊就够了
- 见鬼，我才不去呢！ - 不 你要利用他们，有礼貌地去，
不要求任何回报
把这家伙当做是个礼物送给丹尼
- 就当是帮了个忙 - 那家伙简直是头猪！
相信我
这次交易绝对有所收获
- 准备好迎接明天的大日子了吗？ - 只是个生日而已嘛
是10岁生日，是很特别的！
或许吧
对了，看看我抓到了谁 在屋子周围四处乱跳
- 四处乱蹦？ - 是啊，四处乱跳
谢谢爸爸，它很好
我知道它没有以前的小兔那么可爱
但在我们找到它之前 至少可以让它陪着你
对了，我在想你可以邀请些班上同学 来参加你的生日聚会
- 可以让赫奇小姐来吗？ - 其实她也是策划者之一
- 当然了，是我的主意 - 谢谢爸爸！
雪儿 雪儿.莫特
- 能见到你真是个惊喜 - 你也不是那么难找嘛
总是改不了老习惯啊
最近还好吗 雪儿？
- 有什么事吗？ - 我想给你看点东西
譬如呢？ 一个新的黑帮纹身？
- 要给我看看吗？ - 比那个更重要一些
这个是给丹尼T的礼物
10分钟会客时间
- 一个礼物？ - 她是这么说的
这家伙杀了我的儿子！
快告诉我，你知道这混蛋住在哪
好了，是时候 该走了
她知道
- 你可以晚上回来接着做 - 好的
替我保管好这些
克拉姆太太，
你现在又想干嘛 柏克，又想说什么？
这周末想来我的生日聚会吗？
干嘛 宝贝，她在跟你说话 不是我，自己决定
要我说，好啊
- 酷，我们走吧 - 去吧
泰迪再被欺负流血的话，我要你负责！
- 好的，我会负责 - 好吧
再会了，克拉姆太太
我听到些有趣的消息
是吗，我觉得你马上就会告诉我
只是有人跑去警告了吉米.克拉姆而已
确有其事，你从哪听来的？
你只要到镇里的酒吧 喝杯啤酒就什么都知道了
顺便说一下，那些是过期新闻了 你该更新一下
你这么想？ 那我告诉你些新的
这人可不那么健忘
从不会轻易地平息某件事端
都有些"坏习惯"，大多顽固不讲道理
有人闯入了我们家，这也是种"坏习惯"？
这只是打草惊蛇
不过是有人想吓吓你罢了，你会没事的
- 你是说吉米.克拉姆？ - 当然不是，吉米.克拉姆就是个窝囊废
我知道这附近所有的混蛋 吉米.克拉姆压根排不上号
- 可他老婆的哥哥就完全不同了 - 他又是谁啊？
他自称凯特 也不知道出于什么白痴原因，
住在下游河岸边
开了一家船舶修理厂 不过他什么都不会修
有传言说他负责处理尸体
嘿，如果我是你我会格外小心的 柏克.
我说的都是真的，你听到了吗？
警长知道他吗？
知不知道？ 鬼才知道那两人有没有一起合作
都说凯特总是秘密会见基思
给他汇报消息，帮他抓些小罪犯
让双方都好过些，作为回报 警长总是帮凯特"照料"着他的那些销路
我看都是胡扯
- 谢谢你的历史课 - 听着，我跟这些亡命之徒一起长大，
我想你应该了解你在跟谁打交道
对了，如果你突然来了兴趣
凯特和我一样每天都会在莱米咖啡厅吃早餐
他可能看起来很不起眼 不过记住我告诉过你的
都是真的，这家伙是个疯子
- 嘿，你在哪？ - 听着，会面被安排在一个什么破钓鱼屋
- 你知道我对这东西过敏，不是吗？ - 按计划行事就好了 雪儿
他们派了赛勒斯.汉克斯
你他妈在开玩笑吗？ 我知道他，那家伙是个禽兽！
- 一个彻头彻尾的冷血杀手！ - 别担心那些了，完成会面就好
看看你
- 真是个好地方，赛勒斯 - 是啊 正如你所见的，这地方坐满了"胖子"
事实上我讨厌他们吃东西的样子 食物被洒的到处都是...
- 因为我他妈就是喜欢这地方，你饿了吗？ - 不了，谢谢
嘿，亲爱的，一杯加牛奶的浓咖啡
会不会耽误我们很长时间 去找到这个该死的叛徒呢？
- 他和他的孩子 - 那帮我们抓住他你到底想要什么呢？
- 我什么都不要，他是个礼物 - 礼物是吗？
是个礼物
妓女重生时 开始给我们礼物了？
我用过去的几年时间弄到了正确的仪器
完美的合伙人和地点
我们现在只需要重新分配
你他妈把我当成傻子了，雪儿.
看来在这美丽诱人的身体里 藏着一个天才啊
- 那卧底在哪？ - 我们达成协议了吗？
- 那卧底在哪？ - 我们达成协议了吗，赛勒斯？
你还有5秒钟时间在我把你的脑袋 穿过桌子砸进地板之前
别他妈耍我  雪儿.
那该死的卧底在哪？
你干嘛呢？
- 做清洁 - 清洁？
屋里乱的不像样了
- 真高兴你意识到了 - 你来干什么？
我是来告诉你关于柏克，那女孩的父亲
- 我希望你离他远一点 - 你给我带东西了吗？
卡西, 我必须得警告你，离柏克远一点！
- 知道了 - 好的
- 我没随身带着那些东西，对不起帮不了你了 - 没带，呵...
- 我觉得你他妈就是在胡扯！ - 我希望你能够拜托那些！
别胡扯了！
- 去冲个澡，吃点东西就好了 - 没带你他妈来这干嘛？
你去冲个澡吧，凯特，看看你自己！
够了，卡西，自己振作起来 我他妈已经受够了！
嘘嘘嘘，安静点！
- 孩子已经睡了，你想把他吵醒吗？ - 别担心
不要制造噪音，我要走了 不要再有什么了
我该走了，不会再有了，卡西
嘿，凯特
- 最近还好吗？ - 怎么了？
- 听着哥们儿，我需要你帮个忙 - 帮个忙？
让我猜猜 你们没有足够的人手来倒垃圾了？
我希望你停止给我老婆那些东西
看看她，萎靡的不成样子
或许是你该更尽职地照顾她吧
- 你睡了吗？ - 像婴儿一样熟睡
- 有什么消息吗？ - 凯特.博丁. 我按你的要求调查了他
有过几次逮捕记录，没有定罪 你需要详细资料吗？
- 不，我想不用了 - 不过还有件事，柏克.
雪儿.玛丽莫特 前什里夫波特机车帮成员，
因向安哥拉走私毒品两次被捕
她过去的组织里，有你的老朋友 丹尼T.
最近突然间又有丹尼T的部下 在什里夫波特活动，你要小心了
兰迪，给我一张她的照片
- 我明早一到办公室就给你发E-mail. - 谢了，兰迪
这个叫赛勒斯的，你认识他吗？
- 是的，我认识他 - 之前和他睡过吗？
见鬼！
操！
这应该会很有趣
你我还没正式见过面呢
- 这是什么？ 引见仪式吗？ - 是的，没错
我不会问你的名字 我个人认为名声才更重要
对某些人而言
对你也应该是如此 鉴于你之前建立的坏名声
你在人群面前痛打了那可怜孩子的父亲
也惹毛了许多当地人 他女儿动手打了吉米的儿子，你相信吗？
什么样的父母才会教自己的孩子那样做呢？
听着，我不想有更多麻烦了
还有什么需要我仔细考虑的吗？ 我觉得我能闻见空气中的火药味
那些跟我有个人恩怨的，最好冲着我来，
- 我不想我的孩子被牵扯进来 - 牵扯进来？
我有点听不懂了
你已找到了
- 看见马场了吗？ - 嗯哼
马场正是我们的住处所在
我们家被某个可悲的胆小鬼闯入了，
你偷走了一个小女孩的玩具 猫 还戳破了汽车轮胎
那他妈是我的家，
无论谁再敢过来，会发现我站在门口
好的
我觉得你有些激动了，
她只是在联系一位没有预约上的医生罢了
你已经被警告了，博丁
嘿，告诉你女儿勇敢点 不需要害怕，她有这么一位硬汉老爸
见到你真高兴
吃完你的早餐吧
- 你在干嘛，凯特？ - 这家伙认为我只当成私人恩怨
已经来不及了，他们今晚就要行动了
路瑟！
快过来！
你还好吗？ 孩子？
把猫放下，慢慢地站起来
路瑟!
路瑟！
- 抓到你了 - 嘿，柏克
柏克
你还好吗？ 能听见我吗？
你还清醒吗？
能听到我吗？ 现在能听到我了吗？
你肯定能
用钢击打人是很有技巧，很微妙的，
你挥的太用力或是太快 都会把那人的脑袋卸下来
- 这可是非常微妙的步骤 - 是啊，干得不错 卢
你要是做出什么愚蠢的事情 凯特 一定会很生气的
换你们也会生气吧，很生气
很有趣，你是个有趣的人 , 柏克.
你真他妈是个有趣的人
你这自作聪明的混蛋！
喜欢这样吗？ 嗯？
大家其实都知道你是个警察 柏克
你走起路来像警察
你开起飞机来像个警察
你闻起来甚至也像个警察
- 凯特 可能快回来了 - 我他妈才不在乎!
这我做主，你听见了吗？
你听见了吗？ 谁在照看你那该死的孩子呢？
你女朋友？ 雇了个保姆？
或是她独自在家，等着你回去，
回家去安慰她可怜的灵魂
再读几篇睡前故事，哈哈...
怎么回事儿？
狗娘养的!
我回家以后
的确会给她读几篇睡前故事
而这就是故事的结尾
快告诉我我们为什么要离开？为什么？
我知道我欠你一个道歉 可是我们没有时间解释了
上学怎么办？
我们明早就能拿到你的档案，没关系的
我们为什么要离开？
- 发生了什么事？ - 没什么事，他们要我马上回到城里有新的生意
- 我需要检视一个案子 - 不，你说过妈妈希望我们住在这的！
- 那正是你所说的？ 记得吗？ - 是的，这有事改变了好吗，有改变
我很抱歉 麦蒂，对不起！
你是个骗子
- 凯特. - 你一定就是赛勒斯了
- 雪儿告诉了我很多关于你的事 - 是吗，真贴心
那混蛋在哪？
他住在12号高速公路以南3公里的地方
- 一个马场中 - 我会给你们画幅地图的
路线，甚至房子里的构造
我们不需要什么地图 我们需要你的住处 凯特
嘿，来看看这
这是怎么回事？ 这么多人在这？
- 当这他妈是个聚会吗？ - 我怎么会知道，这帮人就直接闯来了
准备好给我们带路了吗 凯特？
不，我们不会去的
- 再说一遍！ - 听着，警察要抓的是我
我是不会在任何公共场所露面的
我猜你看不到 我一枪打进那叛徒的嘴里了
应该是的
那个孩子怎么办？
应该赶尽杀绝，对吗 凯特？
没错，不能留下目击证人
- 她得跟我们一起走 - 不，这在协议之外
她得给我们带路，我会把她带回来的
- 我可以帮你养它们一周左右 - 谢了，哥们儿，我欠你一个大人情
还有什么要告诉我的吗？
是的，不过恐怕没有那么多时间了
好吧，我去把它们装车了
- 你好啊 警长 - 你好吗 凯特？
- 还好 - 最近忙什么呢？
大卖了一笔，所以我们可以庆祝一下
- 恭喜了 - 谢谢
我在撞球厅还有约
- 回见了 - 好的，谢谢你的威士忌
记得别找麻烦
是的，长官!
我们去20分钟，想都别想要逃跑，懂了吗？
去吧，给你男朋友打电话
他是怎么搞的？
- 麦蒂! - 走走走，上啊!
麦蒂!
爸，怎么回事？
我要你呆在这下面好吗，打911，
告诉他们你是谁，你在哪，
告诉他们有个持枪的人想要闯进房子里好吗
去吧
你去
在这里
麦蒂!
凯特 这有些不对劲！
- 怎么不对了？ - 房子附近到处都是枪声！
冷静点，告诉我发生了什么
- 该死，这枪声，我先挂了！ - 你就呆在那告诉我发生了什么！
麦蒂, 快跑!
救命啊!
- 你还好吗？ - 求你了，救救我！
那有个人，他在袭击我爸爸
- 去帮帮他！ - 好了好了，听我说，听着！
这些人他们根本就不在乎你 他们会杀了你，懂了吗？
你必须跟我走，好吗？ 你必须跟我走，来！
该死，你这懦夫!
爸爸!
放开我!
麦蒂!
来人啊，帮帮我！ 爸爸， 救我！
- 柏克 发生什么事了？ - 他们袭击了我家，带走了我女儿
他们绑架了她，乘船走的水路，在河上
- 袭击了你家是什么意思？ - 他们伏击了我们，5-6个人全副武装
- 想要杀了我们 - 她被带到了河上？ 你知道谁带走了她吗？
柏克!
快找医生来！
你会没事的！
该死的亡命徒！
警长，听无线电，柏克 的女儿在线上！
- 柏克 , 你女儿正在线上！ - 过来继续给伤口施压！
- 说吧，麦蒂. - 告诉我你没事！
爸，爸，求你了，让我离开这里！ 快点...
别担心宝贝，相信我，我这就来！
- 你需要告诉我是谁带走了你？ - 我不知道，是个黑头发的女人
好了亲爱的，现在我们这么做，等你出去后...
就藏起来，躲在哪里，一辆车或是什么
好的，我知道了！
麦蒂？
接线员，我要你每30秒检查一遍线路！
不用了警长，相信我 一架直升机会更快些
有更好的主意了，我们追踪嫌疑人 让直升机赶紧起飞！
- 10哩内的公路全部封闭！ - 使用10哩程无线电
切换至25哩程无线电
告诉他们 我们在找一名白种人女性驾驶员 驾船逃离...
我们在追捕一名白种人女性驾驶员 驾船逃离...
- 袭击你家的那些人，他们现在在哪？ - 就在那了
- 你怎么知道？ - 相信我，我知道的
雪儿 , 快点接电话!
跟我在修理厂见面！ 到底发生了些什么？
把你的电话给我！
所有人安静！
爸爸，我们停下了，我真的很害怕！快点好吗？
我能看到有栅栏，
我们停在一座仓库里
柏克!
好了
- 来吧，没事了，把你的手给我 - 走开!
该死!
接电话，宝贝，快点！
雪儿, 我一直在给你打电话，你他妈怎么回事儿！
- 到底发生了什么？ - 什么都发生了！
这话是什么意思？ 赛勒斯呢？其他人呢？
- 我不知道！ - 你把他们扔在那了？
- 我抓到那孩子了 - 什么？
那孩子在我手上，就在这
你把她带到这来了？
你把那孩子带到这来了？
你是智障吗？ 雪儿？
别! 不要！
- 凯特! - 别什么？ 婊子！
你会毁了这计划的!
- 你不能这么做! - 你竟然把她带到这来!
你毁了整个计划! 你他妈搞砸了！
为什么把这孩子带到这来？
你他妈把她带来干嘛？ 别他妈用手碰我!
你把目击证人带到这来了！
快闭上嘴，然后让她安静点！ 你能做到吗？
- 你们来这干嘛？ - 你听说枪战的事了吗？
- 没有啊，什么枪战？ - 老马场那边的枪战
- 不，你听说了吗？ 没有
好几个人死了，一个孩子失踪了
总之，这里没有枪声
你们最好赶紧回家去， 嘿 吉米 快带她回家去
- 告诉我你与这件事毫无关系 - 我与这件事毫无关系！
你也许有些不安和担心吧 可现在的确该回家了！
- 吉米. - 卡西, 过来，我们走
我们也住在这，你知道我是什么意思吧？
放我走!
我们没有别的选择!
求你了，你正处于危险中! 让我走!
卡西 这与我们无关!
让我走!
这到底发生了什么？
你不想被牵扯进来 卡西
- 卡西. - 你疯了！
知道吗，你疯了！
卡西，这都是你引起的！
别介入其中!
卡西，你给我离着远点！ 我警告你！
爸爸! 爸爸！
坐下，坐下！ 你以为我他妈的想这样吗？
我刚刚枪杀了我的妹妹!
快停车!
告诉港口操作室，断开大桥，
重复， 断开大桥
不!
该死！ 连接大桥！ 连接大桥！
爸！ 爸！ 你还好吗？
- 都不许开枪，有个孩子在桥上！ - 停下，求你了！别伤害他　！
爸爸！ 不要啊！
- 你还好吗？ 爸爸！ - 马上给我回到车里去!
- 我不想你看到这些! 快上车去！ - 你没必要这么做的! 快停下！
- 停下! - 回车里去!
- 放过他吧 , 求你了! - 快回车里去!
快上车不然我打烂他的脸!
你闻到空气中的火药味了？
你确定闻到火药味了？
现在你能确定了！
让我给你你的名声吧！
她刚刚救了你一命
我们回家吧 麦蒂
我在外面等着你 丹尼
我会一直等着你的！
最后防线
(MOTORCYCLE ENGINES ROARING)
(ROCK MUSIC BLARING)
They're in.
TURRIE: This will make me happy.
JOJO: How much should we cook?
This batch will yield 30 pounds.
Move, tweak.
Are you fucking kidding me? Don't be lighting that shit up in here.
Take it outside, Jojo.
All right.
Deal we had was 50 keys by a plane, JT.
Your guy gets held up at Port Arthur, that is not my problem.
Danny T will appreciate that.
Everything set, Dalton? Yeah, all good.
Same plane, same pilot, same price. Good.
Fuck this half-ass plane.
We have 20 hardcore motherfuckers
who can drive this shit to Tucson.
PHIL: Well, my way is the safe way.
Your call, Danny.
Look, you're my kid, but we're doing it Dalton's way.
Everybody, let's start packing this shit up.
We're out of here in 30 minutes. Let's go.
(COOKS CHATTERING)
Let's roll, boys.
(CHATTER OVER RADIO)
Go, go, go.
AGENT 1: Go, go, go. AGENT 2: Get your hands up.
We need to go. We need to go.
DEA! Show me your hands!
Don't move. Don't move. Show me your hands!
Get 'em up! Get on the ground!
Jesus Christ. Somebody give me a 20 on my agent inside.
AGENT: Don't move. MAN: All right.
AGENT: Don't do it! Don't do it!
You were one of us, you fucking rat!
Move. Move.
JOJO: What the fuck was that?
(MOANING)
Jojo, let's get the fuck out of here.
Drop your weapon!
(CLAMORING)
COP: Freeze.
He's undercover!
Stand down!
Stand the fuck down!
Put your fucking weapon down!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(LAUGHING)
Take that, motherfucker!
All units, I got two on the move.
Dark green muscle car heading south-east on St. Bernard towards MLK.
Agent in pursuit. I repeat, agent in pursuit.
What the fuck was that?
Fuck! There's cops all over the fucking place.
Fuck! Fuck!
Come on, Dalton.
You wanna play chicken, motherfucker? Let's do this.
(GRUNTS)
Out of this car, Danny.
Out of the car!
You rat, motherfucker!
PHIL: Put the gun down.
Drop it, Jojo.
Drop the gun. Drop it!
Ahh!
COP: Drop the gun.
Stand down! Stand down!
He's DEA! Get him away.
Stand down.
Fuck you.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
You were one of us.
You murdered my son, you motherfucker.
You're dead. Your kids are fucking dead.
He was down. He was done.
He went for his gun. That's protocol, Broker.
Broker. Broker!
Don't walk away from me. Broker!
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
Cool hat.
Thanks.
Give it back.
You scared?
I said, give it back.
You want it? Come get it.
What are you gonna do about it? Cry?
Go on.
Cry.
I asked you twice.
Twice what, loser?
I asked twice.
(GROANS)
Yeah, if you're gonna take the job, you might as well do it right.
There's all kinds of wood you can get here.
You got virgin cypress, you got longleaf pine,
you got that pressure treated pine.
Well, that's my favorite one.
Now, anybody want to use the cheapest shit they can find,
might as well buy the shit from IKEA.
Look at this. Mites done ate all through it.
Man! (PHONE RINGING)
Wonder why you got to do the job again every two years.
That's some shit. Look at this. Hello.
I'll be right there.
Something wrong?
Oh, something at Maddy's school.
You okay to finish? Yeah, man.
I'm working with you, not for you, Broker.
Hey, Broker, don't sweat it. It's probably nothing.
Yeah, you could be right.
PRINCIPAL: I hear you, but you need to stay calm about this.
CASSIE: Stay calm? I don't feel calm,
so why the hell should I stay calm?
No, 'cause it makes no logical damn sense.
Now I want this thing settled, and I mean now.
JIMMY: It's gonna be, honey.
But getting yourself all wound up like this ain't helping.
Who's that, huh? That's right. Just listen to Jim.
Who's that? You know him? Huh?
PRINCIPAL: I don't know.
Is that the father of the goddamn little girl? Are you the father?
Mr. Broker?
What happened?
Maddy's fine. She's in the classroom. Will you come with me?
CASSIE: I want to see my boy.
Teddy, baby, you okay? JIMMY: Cassie!
Look at this. Does it hurt? I know it does.
Look, there's blood all over his goddamn new shirt, Jimmy.
That's why you gotta watch
the sneaky little bitches on the playground.
Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey.
Hey, what, huh? Hey, what? You wanna say something?
Hey, hey, hey. You wanna say something to me?
Why don't we just let them leave the building?
Why is the sheriff here?
For Cassie Bodine.
Last time we had a scene with Cassie, she threatened the principal.
Their son is a special needs case.
By the way, I'm Susan Hetch, school psychologist.
Phil Broker.
Listen, you've got a great girl.
You all right?
So, what happened?
I warned him two times, like I was supposed to.
SUSAN: The schoolyard monitor said she saw Maddy hit Teddy pretty hard,
like she knew what she was doing.
He started it. He's a bully.
Maddy, come on. Hey.
Maybe this is my fault.
I taught her to defend herself.
Think it's good teaching your little girl to fight?
No.
Defend herself though, yeah.
Hey, Maddy, do you mind waiting in the hall, just for a minute?
Yes, ma'am. Thank you.
So, Why'd you guys move up here?
It's a little remote for most people.
She wanted a horse.
(CHUCKLES)
Maddy's mother grew up around here, so
thought it'd be a good place to start rebuilding.
Her file says that your wife died fairly recently.
Last year? Yeah.
It's been hard on her.
Her mom was sick for a while.
Anything else?
Why has he been picking on me?
Yeah, he picks on you because he thinks you're different.
But I'm not different
Well, from him you are.
CASSIE: Nothing gets clone about it.
Except this guy here gets walking along.
Nothing happening there. KEITH: Okay.
Oh, well, then do it. Do it! All right.
Hey, Broker. Hey, Jimmy.
Broker! All right, stand by the car, baby.
What's wrong? Just stand by the car, please.
Don't take any shit, Jimmy.
Jimmy, back in the truck, please.
You owe my son a goddamn apology.
Take it easy, like the officer said, okay?
Jimmy, back in the truck, please.
Some sneaky little bitch cheap shots my son.
Somebody owes us a goddamn apology.
That's goddamn right.
Don't call her that, please. Don't call her that.
Can you get in the truck, please, honey?
Don't turn your back on me.
Honey, baby, get in the truck.
Get him, Jimmy. Get him, Jimmy. KEITH: Hey, hey, hey!
Come on, take him down, Jimmy. KEITH: Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Arrest him! Keith! Get off of him. Back off.
What the fuck are you doing?
Get this motherfucker out of here. Sir, move away.
CASSIE: God damn it, what are you doing?
Keith, what the fuck are you doing?
Cassie, shut up.
You're gonna let him get away with that?
It's okay, baby. Get in the truck.
It doesn't look okay. It's okay.
KEITH: Get in the truck.
CASSIE: Go and do something, will you? TEDDY: Are you okay?
Breathe, Jimmy. Jesus Christ!
Yes, mosey on over.
Am I in trouble here? KEITH: No, no.
I saw what happened. He was out of line.
You really had to take him down that hard though?
Embarrassed a man in front of his child, Mr. Broker.
It goes both ways, Sheriff.
She all right?
You all right?
So, you moved into the old Griffin place awhile back?
What you doing to keep busy around here?
There a reason you're asking these questions?
Well, maybe I'm just being friendly.
Or maybe I'm bored, or maybe I'm curious,
or whatever, it doesn't matter.
It's my right to ask.
Things got out of hand, Sheriff. That won't happen again.
Dad.
There's a bunch of teachers watching us right now.
You're a pussy.
What? I said you are a motherfucking pussy.
That's what you are.
(SCOFFS)
You let him make fools out of all of us, in front of everybody.
Now the whole fucking town is gonna know.
Look, I lost my...
You lost your what, Jimmy? You lost your what?
I lost my balance.
You fucking lost your balance.
He spun you, dropped you on your ass.
TEDDY: Mom, don't curse.
Dad tripped just like me.
What's the plan, Jimmy?
Right now, nothing.
We still got Keith on our tail.
CASSIE: Fuck Keith!
How did he buy that new truck?
That's what I want to know. How did he buy that new truck?
Who? Who?
Fucking who?
Him! The motherfucker that put you clown. You forget him?
My God, he put you down so hard.
I gotta see my brother.
Let's just keep this a family matter, Cass.
What do you call him?
(SIGHS)
Yeah, now you're acting all big.
Fucking idiot.
(HARD ROCK MUSIC BLARING)
Come on now, fire that fucking shit up.
Look at you, you dumb motherfucker! (WHOOPING)
Boo! Boo! Boo! Boo! Boo! Boo!
Afternoon.
Tweaker birds, cooking up some shit.
Turn that music off.
Turn that fucking music off! (MUSIC STOPS)
Hey.
How old are you?
Seventeen.
All right, go on. Get out of here.
Are you coming?
They ain't coming. Get the fuck out of here!
(SIGHS) As for you guys...
(SCREAMING)
Fuck! (YELLING)
Oh, fuck.
My name is Gator Bodine.
(MOANING)
Hope I didn't hurt you too badly, sir.
Just wanted you to get a little taste of what's gonna happen to you
if you continue cooking this illegal substance
in my neck of the woods.
Look, man. We didn't mean no disrespect.
This here is just for us, you know.
Oh, I don't doubt it.
Just fun, just kids having fun.
Enjoying life. (SOBBING)
Celebrating.
Well, let me warn you,
I've got a five-gallon can of gasoline out in my truck
that I will happily pour down your fucking throats
if I ever catch you cooking and stinking up my town again.
(SCREAMS)
God, stop!
Now, listen up.
I don't wanna have to kill a bunch of little kids.
You will stand up and run, in any direction you please.
Just not this one.
That clear? Yeah.
All right, now get the fuck out of here!
Go!
Run!
Piece of shit kindergarten operation.
Fucking kids suck.
How are the knuckles, bruiser?
It feels fine now, Dad. Oh, yeah?
Watch out, here comes Maddy Mad-fists. Pow!
Dad. Really?
Mmm-hmm. Really?
(CHUCKLING)
Come on. All right, listen.
I'm proud you stood up for yourself.
You set boundaries with this kid.
(CAT PURRING)
Sounds like a motorboat. What, is he snoring?
Dad?
Yeah.
Were you scared today?
The truth.
There's nothing wrong with being a little scared.
Then why didn't you look scared?
Lots of practice.
Night, Luther.
Dad?
Yes.
What do you think of Miss Hetch?
I'd say she's... I'd say she's all right.
You know what I mean. Yes.
I know exactly what you mean.
Goodnight. Goodnight.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO)
Shit.
Look, you need to cool way down.
I need to cool way down?
You think we're gonna be disrespected by some son of a bitch?
Well, I hate to say it,
but putting your old man on the ground ain't any big thing.
When he was talking to Keith,
I heard him say... What, the fucking sheriff was there?
I heard him say he was living at the old Griffin place.
Fuck.
Can't you go over there and do some things?
Do what things? Mess with their heads,
like you do everyone else.
Scare 'em.
Hey, boss.
We good for the night?
I'll talk lo you two in a minute, all right?
All right.
Good seeing you again, Cassie.
What the hell's wrong with those two?
Never mind 'em. Fucking monkeys is what they are.
Hey. Mmm?
You look a little jumpy. I know.
I need something.
I need a little something
to stop my stomach from knotting up.
You want me to beg?
No.
If I can control it, you can control it, right?
Yeah.
I'll handle that Broker thing.
Thank you.
Planning kids' birthday parties, it's my specialty.
Be happy to take care of it for her.
Thanks.
I'm not very good with those things. Missed half of them.
Don't worry. I'm on it. It'll be fun.
You know, she really likes you, Susan.
It's a bit of a milestone, I'd say.
Do you think you can talk to her sometime?
Of course.
Maddy used to talk to her mom for hours.
I think she'd like to talk to a woman more often.
I'd be happy to.
Thanks.
One more thing,
people around here can do some foolish things.
Meaning?
It's a bit like Appalachia, like feuds, they still exist.
And you're new here.
So I just think it would be best for Maddy
if you would smooth everything over
while it's still fresh in people's minds.
Just two kids working things out.
You can go from two kids and a fistfight
to the emergency room real fast.
I didn't know this town had an emergency room.
Now you're catching on.
Look, people talk.
They decided you're a question mark, so.
Keep it smooth. Check.
You want something around here? I don't think so.
Look, what happened, happened.
We don't want any more trouble.
See, your kid made the trouble. Not ours, yours.
What do we need to do to make this go away, Jimmy?
From you?
I want an apology.
Full apology.
I want you to apologize to my wife,
'cause it's what's right, and my kid, too.
He saw the whole damn thing.
I apologize for what happened.
To them, too.
We good now, Jimmy?
Yeah, all right.
Go on. You've said enough.
(SPITS)
(GENERATOR SPUTTERING)
(GRUNTING) (GENERATOR SPUTTERING)
Go ahead and pump it your own self.
I'll be with you in a minute.
God damn, Mama's freezer.
MAN: There he is.
Fuck!
Still ain't got this piece of shit fixed.
Hey, neighbor, how you doing?
Can I get that pump?
I'm almost done.
See, I need the goddamn pump right now. Did you hear me?
Can I help y'all out here? MAN: No.
We don't need your help.
He's done.
Fill up the truck, Clay.
That's $12.84, sir.
I wasn't done yet.
I think you are.
(SIGHS)
Whatever you're thinking, rethink it.
"Rethink it." He wants me to rethink it.
You ain't turning that back on.
Oh, shit.
You fucked up.
Why don't we step around the side of the building
so I can kick your fucking ass up over your shoulders?
They from around here?
I ain't never seen them.
Who put you up to this?
Nobody.
Bring that over.
Down the hatch.
(PHONE RINGS)
Yeah?
Fuck.
How the fuck did that happen?
His fucking kid goes to my nephew's school! I don't fucking know!
Yeah, I'll deal with it. God damn it!
Dad? Mmm-hmm?
What happened to your hands?
Right there?
Oh, yeah.
Me and Teedo were trying to pull that rusty, old fence out of the ground,
you know, the one behind the stable.
Yeah.
We won, though.
(SIREN WAILS)
KEITH: Afternoon.
Mind stepping out for a minute?
You can stay in there, little girl, this won't take too long.
Is there a problem, Sheriff?
Well, I got a report of an altercation at the filling station.
You know anything about that?
Anybody pressing charges?
No, nobody is pressing any charges.
Then there's nothing worth talking about.
What are you' son?
You WITSEC, huh?
You ex-military, ex-law enforcement?
Ex-what?
Well, if I were ex-military, Sheriff,
I'd probably refer to the answer as "need to know information."
Maybe some people don't need to know.
Here's what you need to know, Broker.
You have got my attention, son.
Get that hand looked at.
You're gonna leave me behind today, as usual?
MADDY: I think so.
PHIL: Making new friends at school?
MADDY: Yeah, I made a lot of friends.
I've learned some cool stuff in science class.
PHIL: I don't believe that
MADDY: Did you know that the trees along the river, bald cypress,
they can grow, like, 100 feet.
PHIL: That is cool.
MADDY: But not as cool as snakes.
Snakes? Yeah.
We've got moccasins' copperheads, diamondbacks.
No king cobras, right?
Dad' no, king cobras are like, from the far east somewhere.
That's a relief.
Dad? Yeah?
Why did we move out here?
Why? Because there's no king cobras.
Come on, look around.
A beautiful house, horse trails, river in our backyard.
Seriously, what else could we ask for?
Wi-Fi.
Wi-Fi?
Yeah, Wi-Fi.
Anyone home?
Your door is open.
Neighbor calling.
That was a tie.
OK.
Maybe. I think you got it.
Do you know "grace"?
She a new friend at school?
The new vocab word from class.
"Grace." Yeah, that's a good one.
I think Mom had that
Yeah, you got a good memory, Maddy.
She did.
The way she dressed, smiled.
Everything about her.
I miss Mom.
Me, too.
I just... I miss her so much that my stomach hurts.
And I get this feeling that she worries about you.
And that she wants you to be happy.
Come here.
Hey.
If you're here, I'm happy.
Come on, what else could I be?
(HORSE NEIGHING)
Come on, catch up.
I find myself always trying to do that.
Luther!
(LUTHER MEOWS)
(NEIGHING)
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Easy, boy, easy. Easy.
Dad?
Dad!
Have you seen Luther?
Luther? No, sweetie.
I don't hear his bell. I'll go look.
Hey. Get back inside.
You should be getting ready for bed.
Don't worry, I'll find him. Off you go.
Okay.
Dad, you know I can't sleep without Luther.
I know, but I need you to try, okay?
I'll find him.
And you'll find Bunny, too? Yes.
I'll find them both.
Hey.
It'll be okay. Okay.
(WHISTLES)
Luther. Come here, kitty. Luther.
"Phil Broker."
Motherfucker!
Nice hair.
"For a few years now, biker gang known as
"the Outcast motorcycle gang led by Danny Turrie."
No! You're done! You're dead!
Holy shit!
Broker, Broker, Broker.
Very nice to meet you, Agent Broker.
(PHIL WHISTLING)
Luther?
Come on.
(BELL DINGING)
Coming through!
Yeah?
Hey, I think I got something big for us.
Big? Like what?
Just get over here as soon as possible.
My shift doesn't end for another three hours.
Then I've got to drive from Shreveport? Gator, shit.
All right, all right. Just make it first thing in the morning, okay?
Everything is changing.
(MOANING)
Yeah!
Remember Jojo?
Jojo Turrie?
Danny T's boy? Of course, I do.
The kid was bat shit.
He was.
Until he got shot by the police 47 times.
Losing your only kid like that.
I hear Danny T is still pretty fucked up about it.
Well, yeah.
Well, they never did catch whoever snitched on Jojo and Danny T.
And?
'Cause it wasn't just a snitch.
It was a goddamn undercover cop.
Just read.
MORGAN: That guy Broker,
he's the snitch they didn't want showing up in the courtroom.
What?
M.C. Dalton, that's his snitch name.
SHERYL: A state narc is living in Rayville. Shit!
Relax, relax. Do you have...
I think he's just living low here with his daughter.
Trust me, this is our shot.
What the hell are you doing here, Broker?
Turn that off.
Hey!
Let's skip the bullshit. Get right to it.
Some small-time amateur crap, going back and forth.
Know anything about it?
I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
Is this fucking amusing to you, Klum?
You think it's fucking funny?
You got your apology.
Me and my little girl are gonna be left in peace.
Don't escalate this any more.
And Klum,
I want my kid's cat back.
Cat?
I don't know nothing about no cat.
Today.
No hair out of place, you understand me?
Good.
A lot of things have changed since you were last here.
Check it out, I got glassware, mantles, generator, exhaust system.
Got it all going on.
Why the fuck do we need Danny T?
We're gonna give him that rat fuck narc
in exchange for state-wide distribution.
Yeah, but, Gator, these guys are fucking bikers.
You can't trust them.
You're gonna give them this guy,
they're gonna turn around and they're gonna kill him.
And then you got nothing.
Look, this means no more small time jobs, no more sweating middlemen.
All we do is cook and get paid.
It's never that easy.
All you have to do is learn a few lines,
go and talk to Danny T's lawyer.
Like hell I am.
You use them. Coming back all humble.
You're not asking for money.
You're giving Danny this guy as a gift, as a favor.
Gator, that guy is a fucking pig.
Shh! Just trust me.
You're gonna get the negotiation of your life.
Ready for the big day tomorrow?
It's just a birthday.
Hey, come on, it's the 10th birthday. It's a special one.
I guess.
Hey, look what I found jumping around.
Jumping around? Yeah, jumping around.
Thanks.
It's nice.
I know it's not as good as the original,
but I thought she might fill in until we find Bunny.
Yep.
You know, I was thinking,
you should have a birthday party with your class.
Can Miss Hetch come?
She's the one who planned it.
My idea, of course.
Thanks, Dad.
Yep.
Sheryl. Sheryl Mott.
Surprise, surprise, surprise.
You're not a hard man to find, Werksey, old habits and all.
How are you doing, Sheryl?
What's up, kid?
I want you to look at something.
Like what?
You got a new gang tattoo that you want to show me?
It's a little bit more important than that.
It's a gift for Danny T.
(LOCK BUZZING)
GUARD: You got 10 minutes.
"A gift," she says.
This guy killed my fucking kid.
Please tell me you know where this motherfucker is.
Guess what? Time to go.
She does.
Hey, you can finish it tonight.
Okay.
Take care of this for me.
Miss Klum?
What are you going to do now, Broker? What do you want to say?
Wanna come to my party this weekend?
What, Teddy? She's talking to you, hon, not me. Come on.
I guess. Yeah.
Cool. Come on, let's go.
All right. Go on.
Teddy got some blood on his shirt. Are you replacing it?
Yeah, I'm replacing it.
All right. I guess that does it.
See you around, Miss Klum.
TEEDO: So, I heard something interesting.
Yeah? Something tells me you're gonna tell me what that is.
Just that Jimmy Klum got his ass whopped. So did his kid.
Fascinating.
Where did you hear that?
Well, you shoot enough pool, drink enough beer in town,
you hear a little bit of everything, Broker.
By the way, that's old news. We shook and made up.
Is that what you think?
Yeah.
I got some new news for you.
People around here don't shake and make up.
It never goes away that easy.
It's old-school in the feuding sense around here.
Hey, someone broke into our house. Is that old-school?
There it is, that's called country payback.
Somebody's just trying to scare your ass out of here, is all.
You'll be all right.
Jimmy Klum, you mean?
Fuck, no. Jimmy Klum is a bitch.
Listen, I know everybody around here,
and Jimmy Klum's bitch ass ain't breaking into shit.
Now, his wife's brother is a whole different story.
Who's his wife's brother?
They call him Gator for some dumb-ass reason.
Lives down by the Rayville watershed.
Fronts as a boat mechanic, can't fix shit.
But the word is he's cooking up that meth.
Hey, if I was you, I'd be real careful around him, Broker.
He ain't true, you hear me?
The sheriff know about him? (LAUGHS)
Know about him?
Man, him and Sheriff Keith got it all figured out.
You see, Gator snitches for Keith,
throws him all the small fish, makes his job easy.
In turn, Sheriff looks the other direction whenever Gator wants to cook.
Some bullshit.
Yeah, thanks for the history lesson.
Listen, I grew up around these rednecks,
and I think you ought to know who you're fucking with.
And in case you got any interest,
Gator eats breakfast nearly every day at Lions café, just like me.
Now, he don't look like much or nothing,
but you remember what I told you,
he ain't true.
Crazy, waiting to happen.
Hey, where are you?
They set the meet at this fucking crayfish shack off Creek Road.
You know I'm allergic to this shit, right?
Just get it done, all right, Sheryl?
The guy they're sending, Cyrus Hanks.
Are you fucking kidding me? I know him. He's a fucking animal, Gator.
He's a fucking stone-cold killer.
Look, don't worry about any of that. Just make it happen.
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
(ALL SINGING)
(ALL CHEERING)
Look at you.
Nice place, Cyrus.
Yeah, well, let's just say I'm comfortable around fat people.
They eat the way gamblers play the slots,
they're fucking oblivious to everything around them.
Plus, I love these fucking things.
Are you hungry?
No, I'm fine.
Sweetheart, black coffee with a little honey.
So, what's it going to take
to find this rat fuck? You know where he is, yeah?
Him and his kid.
And to get him, you want what, exactly?
I don't want anything for the narc.
He's a gift. Oh, he's a gift? He's a gift.
Since when does a meth whore give away gifts?
I've spent the last couple of years
putting together the right equipment,
perfect partner, perfect location.
All we need is distribution, that's the main thing we're after...
(LAUGHING)
You got me fucking fooled, Sheryl.
'Cause underneath this beautiful tweaker body,
you're a fucking genius.
Where's the narc?
Do we have a deal?
Where is the narc?
Do we have a deal, Cyrus?
Come over here.
You got five seconds before I drill your fucking skull into this table
and then into the floor, you understand me?
Don't you fuck with me, Sheryl.
All right.
Where is the fucking narc?
(BOTH LAUGHING) Bye!
Bye.
Hi.
What are you doing?
Cleaning.
Cleaning? Yeah.
It's filthy in there.
Well, I'm glad you noticed.
What are you doing here?
I came to tell you that I dealt with Broker, the girl's father.
I want you to stay away from him.
Hey, you got something for me?
Cassie, I'm trying to tell you something.
Do not go near Broker anymore.
Got it.
Okay.
Well, I'm not holding, so I'm sorry, I can't help you.
You're not holding?
Uh-huh.
Well, I think that's fucking bullshit.
Cassie, why don't you just clean yourself up?
That's fucking bullshit!
Take a fucking shower. Then what the fuck are you doing here?
Eat a sandwich or something.
You take a fucking shower, Gator, look at you!
Cassie, just pull yourself together.
I'm sick of this shit. Hey, hey, hey.
Shh! Teddy is sleeping.
You wake him up, it's gonna be...
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna make any noise, I'm leaving.
No more. I'm done.
No more, Cassie.
Yo, Gator.
How is it hanging, man?
Why?
Listen, man, I need a favor.
A favor?
Look, Jimmy, you know that I already keep your garbage business going.
Man, I need you to stop giving that shit to my wife.
All right? Look at her, man. She's falling to pieces.
Maybe you should do a better job taking care of her.
(PHONE VIBRATES)
Yeah. You sleeping?
Like a baby.
What have you got?
Gator Bodine. I sniffed around like you asked. A couple of arrests.
No convictions. You want details?
No, don't bother.
But there is something, Broker.
Sheryl Marie Mott, ex-biker groupie from Shreveport.
Busted twice for smuggling dope into Angola.
One of those times was to your old pal, Danny T.
All of a sudden, Danny T's skank is hanging out in Rayville.
Really?
Send me a picture, would you?
Yeah, first thing at my desk, I'll email you Mott's file.
Thanks, man.
MORGAN: So, this guy Cyrus,
you know him?
Yeah, I know him.
Mmm-hmm. Did you fuck him?
(CHUCKLES)
Ugh.
Oh, shit.
Fuck!
This should be interesting.
We've never been properly introduced, you and me.
Is that what this is, an introduction?
Yeah, that's right.
Well, I won't ask your name.
I personally believe your reputation is the most important thing.
To some people. Yeah.
Maybe it should be for you, too.
You've worked up a pretty bad rep around here,
beating up that poor kids father in front of him.
It pissed off some of the locals.
And his daughter beat up Jimmy's kid. Can you believe that?
Now, what kind of parent would teach a kid to do something like that?
Look, I don't want any more problems.
Okay.
Anything else you're thinking hard about?
'Cause I can smell the wood burning.
If someone has an issue with me, keep it there.
I don't want my kid involved.
Involved?
(INHALES)
I'm a little lost.
Well, let's get you found.
See the house,
the house where we're living,
the house that was broken into by some pathetic coward
who stole a little girl's toys, the cat, slashed a tire.
See, that's my fucking house.
Anyone who comes around again will find me standing in it.
Okay.
(PHONE RINGING)
Well, I think you're reaching.
Just connecting dots that are not there.
You're on notice, Bodine.
Hey, you should tell your little girl to be brave.
She's got nothing to worry about with such a tough daddy around.
Nice meeting you.
Finish your breakfast.
(PHONE BEEPS)
What the fuck were you doin', Gator?
Fucker is making it personal.
Yeah, well, we're on.
It's happening tonight.
(YELPS)
(BARKING)
(TAPPING)
(RATTLING)
(BANGING)
(CAT MEOWS)
Luther?
Hello, there.
Hey, boy.
(GUN COOKING)
Put the kitty down.
Get up really slow.
Luther?
Got you. Hey, Broker.
My old fucking Broker.
How you doing, man?
Can you hear me?
Huh?
You in there?
Do you hear me? Do you hear me now?
Bet you do.
That's the tricky thing with this rebar, especially the nine gauge.
You swing it too hard, too fast,
just takes your whole fucking head off, man.
It's a very delicate operation.
Hey, you did all right, though, Lew.
Gator'd be pissed if we did something really fucking stupid.
He must be pissed at you two quite a lot.
That's funny. You're a funny guy, Broker.
You're a really funny fucking guy.
You smart-ass motherfucker.
Fucking wise-ass.
LEWIS: How do you like that, huh?
Everybody had you figured for a cop, Broker.
You walk like a cop, you fight like a cop,
you even smell like a fucking cop.
Come on.
Hey, man, Gator'll be here soon. That's it...
I don't give a shit! I'm calling the shots! You hear me?
Hey! Can you hear me?
Who's watching your fucking kid, huh?
Who's watching your kid?
Your girlfriend?
She got a babysitter?
Or is she at home all by herself,
just waiting on you to come tuck her sorry-ass in
and read her a bedtime story?
What the fuck!
You're dead!
Motherfucker!
(SCREAMS)
When I get home, I am gonna tell my girl a bedtime story.
This is how it ends.
(PURRING)
Just tell me, why are we going? Why?
I owe you an apology, I know, but we don't have time to get into that.
What about school?
We'll send for your records in the morning. It's fine.
Send for them? No, why are we going?
What's wrong? Nothing's wrong.
They need me back in the city. It's new business.
I need to review a case. No!
You said Mom wanted us to live here.
That's what you said, Dad. Remember? Yeah, I did. I did.
Things changed, darling. Things changed.
I'm sorry, Maddy.
I'm sorry.
You're a liar.
(MOTORBIKES AP ROACHING)
Gator.
You must be Cyrus.
Sheryl's told me a lot about you.
Has she?
That is sweet.
Where is the fuck-up?
SHERYL: He's about three miles south of Route 12.
Rubber plantation.
I can draw you a map, trail, even the inside of the house.
No, I don't need a fucking map. We ain't driving, Gator.
Hey, check this one out.
What the fuck is this?
This many people here, this a fucking party?
I don't fucking know. Motherfucker just showed up with all of them.
CYRUS: You ready to show us the way, Gator?
No, I'm not going.
Come again?
Look, the first person they're gonna be looking for is me,
so I'm not gonna be anywhere near the site.
I'm gonna be in a public place.
Guess you don't get to see me shoot the rat tuck in the mouth.
Guess not.
What about the kid?
It's one-stop shopping, right, Gator?
That's right.
No loose ends.
She's coming with me.
No, that's not the deal.
No, she's gonna show us the way. I'll bring her back.
Be back.
(HORN HONKING)
Listen, I can only hold them about a week.
Thanks, Teedo, you're a big help.
Is there anything you need to tell me?
Yeah, there is, but not now. I got a lot of heat.
All right, then, let me go load up these nags.
Howdy, Sheriff. Hey, Gator.
How you doing? All right.
Keeping busy, I hope.
Yeah.
That's good.
Just made a big sale, so I thought we'd celebrate.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
MORGAN: Well, I got a date with a pool table.
So I'll be seeing you.
All right.
Thanks for the whiskey.
Of course.
You keep out of trouble, now.
Yes, sir.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
Twenty minutes.
Don't even think about not being here, you understand me?
Yeah. Go call your boyfriend.
Hey!
(COCKING GUNS)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(HORSE NICKERING)
(YELLING)
Motherfucker! Come on, you fuck!
(GROANING)
(YELLS)
Where the fuck is he?
Fuck.
(HONKING HORN)
(GUN FIRES)
Maddy!
Go, go, go.
Dad, what was that? Shh!
Dad, what was that?
Go.
I need you to stay down here, okay, Maddy?
Dial 911.
Tell them who you are, where you are.
Tell them there's a man with a gun trying to get into the house, okay?
Go.
(LINE RINGING)
(FOOTSTEPS PASSING)
911. What is your emergency?
Go.
(GASPS)
Hey!
No!
She's getting away!
Maddy!
(PHONE RINGS)
Hey.
Gator, man, shit's gone wrong out here.
What do you mean "shit's gone wrong"?
There's too many gunshots all over the fucking place.
Whoa, whoa, Sheryl, just slow down. Tell me what's happening.
Fuck this noise, man. I'm out.
Just stay there and tell me what's happening!
(SIRENS WAILING)
Ahh!
Maddy, run! Run!
Help! Help! Help!
Help!
Help, please! Help me, please! Hey, you okay?
Please help!
There's a man, and he's hurting my dad back at our...
Okay, okay, listen to me.
Listen. These guys, they don't give a shit about you, all right?
They're gonna kill you. Do you understand?
You got to come with me, okay?
You have to come with me! Come on.
Fucking pussy!
Not okay! Dad! No! Listen!
(GROANING)
(BONES CRUNCHING) (SCREAMS)
Fuck!
MADDY: Let me go!
Let go of me!
Maddy!
No, let me go! Dad!
Maddy! Maddy!
Come on.
Shit.
Maddy!
Help, please! Dad!
Dad, help!
(SIRENS WAILING)
Broker?
What the hell's going on?
They hit the house.
They took my girl.
By boat. Headed south towards Blue Cove.
What do you mean "hit the house"?
An ambush. Five, six men. All armed.
Tried to kill us.
She's on the river? You know who took her?
(HONKING HORN)
Broker? Broker!
Need a medic!
Dispatch, I got a...
You'll be okay, Teedo.
Fucking rednecks.
Sheriff, get on the radio. It's Broker's daughter on dispatch.
Broker, your daughter's on the radio.
Get compression on this wound.
OPERATOR: Maddy, go ahead.
Maddy, tell me you're okay.
Dad? Dad, Dad, please get me out of here, Daddy. Please?
Don't worry, baby. Trust me. I'm coming.
First, you need to tell me who took you.
I don't know. Just some lady with black hair.
Okay, baby. Here's what we're gonna do.
When they take you out, you need to hide the phone.
Okay.
Look for something. A landmark, anything.
Okay. Okay.
Dad... Dad...
Maddy.
Maddy?
Fuck!
Dispatch, listen here, I need you to check back every 30 seconds.
No need to, Sheriff. Track my cell.
Get a state chopper. You'll get there faster.
KEITH: Got a better idea, track his cell.
Let's get the troopers in on this.
I need a bear in the air, and every road within 10 miles shut down.
Go for 25, work your way in.
KEITH: 25-mile radius. Work our way in.
Tell them they're looking for a 20-foot
Boston Whaler, solo female driver,
and a center console.
20-foot Boston Whaler, solo female driver, center console.
Now, these men that attacked your house, where are they now?
They're right there. How do you know?
Trust me. I know.
Sheryl, answer your fucking phone!
Just meet me at the fucking shop! What the fuck's going on?
Give me the phone.
(SIREN BLARING)
KEITH: Quiet down, now.
(LINE RINGING)
Daddy? Maddy.
Daddy, we're stopping. I'm really scared. Please hurry.
I see two big fans.
And we've stopped in a barn.
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
KEITH: Broker!
Broker, you need to tell us, now.
Okay.
Come on. It's okay. It's okay. Just give me your hand.
Go away!
Fuck!
God!
(GROANING) Fuck!
Pick up, baby.
Come on. Come on, Maddy.
Sheryl, I've been calling you. What the fuck?
What the fuck happened?
Everything fucking happened.
What the fuck does that mean?
Where's Cyrus? Where's everyone?
I don't fucking know.
You left them there?
I got the kid.
What? I have the kid.
The kid is here.
MORGAN: You brought her here?
You brought the kid here?
Are you retarded, Sheryl?
Don't!
Don't, Gator!
Don't what, bitch?
What the fuck, Gator?
It's over. Come on, this is over.
MORGAN: You brought the fucking kid here.
You fucked this up!
SHERYL: This is not what you do, man!
You fucking brought a witness here?
You do not kill a kid, Gator.
The only fucking chance we had, you fucked up!
You brought fucking Cyrus into this!
Why did you bring the kid here?
Why the fuck did you bring her here? Gator. Gator.
Get your fucking hands off me!
You brought a fucking witness here, huh?
All right. Damn it.
Just shut the fuck up and keep her quiet.
Can you do that?
What y'all doing here?
Did you hear about the shooting?
No, what shooting?
Up at the old Griffin place?
No, I didn't hear about it. No. You didn't hear about it?
Word is people are dead and a child's missing.
No shit.
Well, no shooting going on here.
So maybe y'all better go home. Hey, Jimmy, you gonna take her home?
Come on. Come on.
Tell me you didn't have anything to do with it.
I didn't have anything to do with it.
Now, maybe you're a little high right now. You're not thinking straight.
But it's time to go home, okay?
Jimmy! Cassie, come on, let's go.
We live here, too. You know what I mean?
Shit, I got to get you out of here.
Let go of me.
No, I'm not gonna let go... Let go of me!
SHERYL: I'm trying to help you. Stop it.
MADDY: But I can't. My daddy...
SHERYL: We don't have a choice. We don't have a choice.
MADDY: Please, he's in trouble! SHERYL: No, no, no!
MADDY: Let me go! Let go of me!
JIMMY: Cass, it ain't none of our business.
MADDY: No, let me go find my dad!
Let go of me!
What the hell's going on here?
You don't wanna get into this, Cassie.
Uh-uh.
JIMMY: Cassie.
All right, Gator. Be cool, man. All right? You're crazy.
Do you know that? You're crazy.
No, she's staying here!
She's not!
Cassie, you fucking started this!
I didn't ask for any of this! Yeah, man!
Just stay out of this!
She's staying with me! Let go of her!
She is not staying with you! Cassie, you stay the fuck out of this!
Let go of her!
Cassie, I'm warning you!
(GUN FIRES)
(GASPS)
JIMMY: Cassie?
Cassie!
No!
Stop the car.
Dad! Dad! Dad!
Get down! Get down! Please, stop!
Get the fuck down! Do you think I fucking wanted this?
I just shot my fucking sister!
Dad!
Just stop the car!
Dispatch, tell the operator of the intercoastal bridge, to open the bridge.
Repeat. Open the bridge.
(BELL DINGING)
MADDY: No! Fuck it!
(SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE)
God damn it.
Close the bridge! Close the bridge!
Dad! Dad, you okay?
No, stop please. Just...
Nobody shoots, there's a child on the bridge.
Stop, please! Don't hurt him.
Daddy! Stop!
Dad, are you okay? Dad.
Get back in the car, right now!
I don't want you to see this! Get in the fucking car!
You don't have to do that! Just stop it!
Pop that trunk. Please, just stop it!
Get the fuck in the car!
Just leave him alone, please? Get in the fucking car!
Please! Daddy, I'm scared!
Get in the car before I blow your fucking brains out!
God damn it.
You smell the wood burning, Bodine?
You smell the fucking wood burning?
Now you connecting the dots?
I'll teach you about reputation.
She just saved your life.
Let's go home, Maddy.
PHIL: See you on the outside, Danny.
I'll be waiting.